LUIS VINICIUS B. SILVA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

CONTACT

in linkedin.com/in/luisvinicius

viniborges@yahoo.com.br



github.com/viniborges



+55 (43) 98810-7869

SKILLS

C#, .NET/NET Core, Web API, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, SQL Server, Oracle PL/ SQL, MongoDB, Redis, RabbitMQ, NUnit, Git, Docker, Kubernetes.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's Degree

FATEC - Taquaritinga

2007-2010

Data Processing

Associate's degree

ETEC Elias Nechar

2005-2006

Technical Computing

LANGUAGES

English: basic to intermediate

Portuguese: native

PROFILE

Passionate developer (since 2010) and tech enthusiast who is always up to learn about new things. Experienced system developer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in .NET/.NET Core with C# (winforms, webforms, MVC, Web API, Minimal Api), Visual Basic, Classic ASP, SQL Server, Oracle PL/SQL, Git, Docker, Kubernetes, Javascript, AngularJs, HTML, CSS.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Sr. Backend Developer

Golfleet Tecnologia

Jun 2019 - Present

- · Contribution in the development and support of the company's SaaS and microservices solutions.
- Development of RESTful APIs with .NET Core and C#.
- Development of user interfaces with AngularJS, HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript.
- Data management with SQL Server and MongoDB.
- · Messaging queues with RabbitMQ.
- · Redis for data caching.
- Containerization and orchestration with Docker and Kubernetes.
- · Application performance monitoring with Elastic APM.

Systems Analyst

Tata Consultancy Services

Jun 2018 - Jun 2019

- Development of demands in the Itaú Unibanco project using .Net MVC, SQL Server, HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery.
- Test coverage using NUnit.
- Applying agile methodologies with Scrum to ensure continuous and incremental deliveries.

Systems Developer Analyst

Atos

Feb 2015 - Jun 2018

- Working on the Volkswagen project, following the ITIL methodology to guarantee stability and new functionalities for the systems.
- Development in Classic ASP, VB6 and C# with WebForms and MVC on .Net, along with HTML, CSS, JavaScript and JQuery, using SQL Server, Oracle and DB2 databases.

Software Developer

Gelt Tecnologia e Sistemas

Jan 2014 - Feb 2015

 Participation in the development of an ERP business management system using the C# language in ASP.NET, HTML 5, JavaScript, CSS3 and SQL Server database.

Jr. Software Developer

Grupo ExataID

Feb 2010 - Dec 2013

 Development of management systems for collecting and processing data for the sugar and alcohol sector, using the Visual Basic 6 language. Development of mobile applications for the PalmOS platform with AppForge lib.